Back we are in our burger project,
Geri bir saatlik Bergere projemiz var.
time to add some routing to it and use the things we learned in the last course module in a real react
Ona baz rota oluturma zaman ve gerek ders uygulamasnda son ders modlnde
application.
rendiimiz eyleri kullann.
Now definitely feel free to jump ahead from time to time, puase the video and implement some feature
imdi videodan zaman zaman yararlanmaya ve baz zellik uygulamaya ekinmeyin.
I'm about to show you to practice using the router.
Ben size ynlendirici kullanarak uygulama gstermek zereyim.
I want to start by adding a page which allows us to actually check our burger out. Right now, checkout
Bergere'mizi kontrol etmemize izin veren bir sayfa ekleyerek balamak istiyorum, bunun gibi
looks like this,
grnmyor.
we add an ingredient, we click order now we click continue and then we already send a request to the
ve daha sonra talebi arkadan gnderdik ve o burgeri gnderdik ve orada sakladk.
backend to submit that burger and to save it there.
Tkladmz bir madde ekledik, imdi devam et dmesini tkladk
Now I'd like to change this so that I have to actually enter some information in a checkout form
imdi burgeri kaydetmeden nce onu kontrol iin bir miktar
before we really save the burger.
bilgi girmek zorunda kaldm.
So this should be the first other page I want to have, a checkout page.
Bu yzden kontrol sayfasnda grmek istediim ilk sayfa olmal.
I also have a link here at the top which might allow us to navigate there, though we'll probably replace
Ayrca burada stte gezinmemizi salayacak bir balant var, ancak bu modl
this throughout this module with my orders page because that makes more sense.
iin muhtemelen yerini sipariler sayfamzla deitirecek daha mantkl olacandan.
But let's start with the checkout component and let's start with building that in the next lecture.
Ancak, deme bileeniyle balayalm ve bir sonraki konferansta Boulding borcuyla balayalm.
Definitely feel free to jump ahead and build it on your own but also feel free to do it together with
pek ok farkl yol var ama gerekten ynlendirme ile ilgili deil .
me because obviously there are a lot of different ways of creating checkout component and creating
Kesinlikle nceden atlamak ve samalk kendi banza ekinmeyin ama ayn zamanda benimle birlikte yapmaktan
the component itself is a nice practice but not really related to routing.
ekinmeyin, nk akas, kontrol bileeni oluturma ve bileenin kendisi oluturmak iin
See you in the next lecture.
Bir sonraki derside grrz.